<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gillian Yeomans</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gillian Yeomans</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Center: Week 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-4/</guid>
      <description>If you want the rainbow, you&amp;rsquo;ve got to put up with the rain Last week I got a lot of educational value out of motoring through Nand 2 Tetris Part 1, but at the end of the week I noticed that the intensity of working solo through it had left me feeling somewhat isolated. Knowing too that working on a self-directed project can lead to bigger learning payoffs, as you learn to plot your own way through a fog of uncertainty without the guardrails of a curriculum, I decided to pivot to something else for a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Center: Week 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-3/</guid>
      <description>Half way Somehow, inexplicably, I&amp;rsquo;ve reached the half way point of a six week batch. I keep thinking I&amp;rsquo;ve made a mistake and recounting where the weeks have gone, but no, here we are.&#xA;From logic gates to assembly code This week was marked by less variety and more focus, as I ploughed at full speeed into Projects 1-6 of Nand 2 Tetris, building up from the logic gates and Arithmetic Logic Unit I mentioned last week, through to assembling the whole CPU and (simple 🙃) computer architecture, to writing machine code, and then (bonus) writing an assembler in Python to translate from symbolic machine code to binary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Center: Week 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-2/</guid>
      <description>LDN -&amp;gt; NYC The Recurse Center is based in New York and pre-Covid all attendance was in person at its office space, the &amp;lsquo;Hub&amp;rsquo;, in Brooklyn. Since the pandemic physical attendance has been optional, but given that a lot of the value of RC is the connections you make and the ideas you share, I wanted to attend in person. Circumstances meant I was still at home in London for week 1, but the big thing for me in week 2 was I arrived in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Center: Week 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/week-1/</guid>
      <description>Wello, horld! Earlier this month I decided to leave my job and spend a few weeks at the Recurse Center, working on my programming skills and taking time to think about what I&amp;rsquo;d like to do next.&#xA;Participants aren&amp;rsquo;t required to write a blog about their time here, but it is a great way to document what you&amp;rsquo;ve been doing in this busy period, for your future self if nobody else.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
